The groove is on the move.
Kronk's New Groove is a animation, comedy, family
film directed by Saul Blinkoff.
Kronk, now chef and Head Delivery Boy of Mudka's Meat Hut, is
fretting over the upcoming visit of his father.
Kronk's father always disapproved of young Kronk's culinary interests and wished that
Kronk instead would settle down with a wife and a large house on a hill.
Kronk (voice), played by Patrick Warburton.
Ms. Birdwell (voice), played by Tracey Ullman.
Yzma (voice), played by Eartha Kitt.
Kuzco (voice), played by David Spade.
Pacha (voice), played by John Goodman.
Chicha (voice), played by Wendie Malick.
Kronk's New Groove (also known as The Emperor's New Groove 2: Kronk's New Groove) is a 2005 American animated direct-to-video
musical comedy film animated by Toon City Animation and released by Walt Disney Home Entertainment on December 13, 2005.
The film is the sequel to The Emperor's New Groove (2000), with David Spade, John Goodman, Eartha Kitt, Patrick Warburton
and Wendie Malick returning from the first film, and John Mahoney and Tracey Ullman voicing new characters.
It was also the last film to feature the voice of John
Fiedler, who died six months before it was released.
The film explores themes of friendship, competition, sequel, hilarious.
The tone is lighthearted.